I'm sick of walking!
Hang in there.
Don't wanna! Carry me!
Hey, Inaba.
Come on, Taichi!
Can you give me a hand?
She's going through an episode.
I don't wanna walk anymore...
Not my problem. You deal with it.
Hey, Inaba!
Hey, why are you guys fooling around?
Yaegashi-kun...
If you use this trip as an excuse to do
unspeakable things to
Nagase-san, you'll pay dearly.
Don't make it sound like I'm a bad guy!
Taichi! Carry me!
Isn't there something else
you care about just as much?
Nagase! Cut it out!
Hey, Inaba!
Help me out here!
Inaba!
I can't believe we have to
use a dump like this.
Sorry, it's my fault for losing
at rock-paper-scissors.
Well, you couldn't help it.
Yaegashi-kun, you will
be punished later.
What?
Watase-kun, can you think
of a suitable punishment?
I would love to!
You look happy.
Now, now, now.
We'll all look back on
this as a fond memory.
Right, Inaban?
I don't need any negative memories.
Uh, I'm sorry.
How can you be so bad
at rock-paper-scissors?
You couldn't beat Iori
or Watase, either.
Right, according to my TV
horoscope this morning,
I have the worst possible luck today.
That could be a factor.
Yikes.
The fall would kill you.
With your luck, you need
to be extra careful.
The only reason I'd fall
is if I were to jump off.
Why are you smiling?
You were depressed a second ago.
Well, it feels like it's been ages since
we just chatted about nothing.
What? You don't have to
be so upset about it.
Be quiet!
Are the three of them doing okay?
They're probably fine
since Inaba-chan is recovering.
Anyway...
You look great!
There's something about girls
with long hair in aprons.
You're so laid back that
I'm actually impressed.
What does it take to
never have to worry?
You're pretty good, Nagase.
I do a lot of cooking at home.
Oh...
Yours look a little rough, Inaba.
Oops!
Don't make fun of me!
I'm awesome at this if I try hard enough!
Wanna see?!
Wh-Why are you so excited?
Are you having an episode?
So what if Taichi gave you
a little compliment, Iori?!
You shouldn't be too
happy with yourself!
How did I get pulled into this?
Let's race to see who
can chop these faster!
A-Am I supposed to do that, too?
Don't ask me.
I got the rice.
Oh, you're getting along just fine.
I was right to assign all
of you to the same group.
How do you figure?
Can we start, Fujishima-san?
I'm starving.
Not yet. Wait a little longer.
Hurry up!
The other groups already started eating!
It'll be a little longer.
I just added the last original spice.
Huh?
You're pretty picky about your cooking.
Not always.
Only when it's curry.
Why?
Okay, it's ready!
Delicious!
Hunger is the best spice,
second only to love!
Um, are you listening to me?
I'm too busy eating this good food!
I was listening to every word!
Love is the answer!
You don't mean love in
a weird way, do you?
I wouldn't be too sure about that.
Anyway, Nagase-san...
There's rice on your cheek.
It's okay! It's okay!
I can get it myself!
Oh, that's unfortunate.
Let's focus on eating.
That was so good.
Yeah.
I wouldn't mind going
on a picnic every day.
I guess.
Say, Inaban...
Hey, Inaba!
Are you bleeding?
Look here!
Oh, I didn't notice.
How did you not notice?
What if it gets infected?
I can wash my own hand!
Does anyone have a band-aid?
It's fine. I brought my own.
I'll be back in a bit.
Wait, Nagase!
Man, they need to mind
their own business.
Wh-What is it, Iori?
Inaban, are you...
Huh?
Are you in love with...?
Wait, Inaban!
She knows!
She knows! She knows!
Where did Nagase and Inaba go?
Inaban!
Tell me why...
Inaban...
Are you in love with Taichi too?
Why?
You kept trying to push
Taichi and me together.
You always said that you
wanted us to be a couple.
I knew that you cared about him.
But wasn't that only as a friend?
Why were you trying to get us together?
Did you want to let me have him?
Inaban...
Explain yourself, Inaba Himeko!
Iori, are you having an episo—
What's that mean?! What's that mean?!
What's that supposed to mean?!
If you don't give me an explanation,
I'm no longer your friend!
But...
That's the only way the five
of us can stay together!
Why would you think that?!
Well, when you have a
group of boys and girls,
and love comes in and complicates
things, there will be arguments.
Friendships fall apart.
Aoki loves Yui,
and despite what she says,
Yui doesn't mind his attention.
You're looking for
someone to support you,
and Taichi's naturally inclined to do that.
If the two of you get together,
everything will work out.
Then the five of us will
always be together.
Are you an idiot?
Everything will work out?
I never realized that Inaba
Himeko was such an idiot!
I was always alone.
Always by myself.
But in high school, I made
friends for the first time!
I didn't want to lose those friends!
I didn't know what else to do!
I don't care about that!
If you feel lonely, you
should say something!
If you're worried, say something!
Most people aren't as sharp as you are!
If you want those people
to understand you,
you should say something!
Even if you're worried that
you'll embarrass yourself,
you should still say something!
I can't do that!
If I show people how weak I am,
they won't need me anymore.
I didn't have a choice!
What else was I supposed to do?!
You didn't need to do anything!
I don't believe that!
A worthless, unwanted failure like me...
Don't say "like me"!
Don't talk about yourself like that!
But it's true!
I'm not a good person
like the rest of you!
How do you think that makes me feel
for liking Inaba Himeko?!
I really like you a lot, Inaban. A lot.
If you don't realize that,
I'll say it a million times.
I love you. We all do.
But that's the fake Inaba Himeko
who's strong and knows what she's doing.
I'd like you no matter
what a mess you were.
You're wrong.
You're wrong, Inaban.
You're a much better
person than you realize.
No, that's not it.
That's not the point.
You can't label people as good or bad.
It's not that simple!
Trust me!
If you...
If you think I'm a good person,
you should trust my words!
It's okay, Inaban!
You don't need to do anything.
I'll always be your friend.
No, that's not quite right.
I want to always be your friend!
Please let me be your friend!
I've...
I've always wanted to
hear someone say that.
But it's too late now.
I'd only be a third wheel.
And I don't want to
ruin the StuCS bond.
So I can't go back to the clubroom.
Why not? What makes you think that?
Well, it would be really awkward.
Everyone would feel uncomfortable.
Remember what you just said?
If Taichi and I got together,
everything would work out?
But wouldn't it also work out if you and
Taichi got together instead?
But you and Taichi are a good match.
And I didn't really care about
Taichi in the beginning.
Er, I still don't, really...
Why are you still lying to yourself?!
I'm not lying.
You were trying hard to protect
our friendship, right?
But you love Taichi so much now that
you can't hold yourself back!
The Inaba Himeko I know
would fight for both!
She would never give up,
no matter the odds!
Arrogant and patronizing!
Using people to her advantage!
Willing to do whatever it takes
to accomplish her goal!
That's the Inaba Himeko I know!
Besides, the friendship
between Nagase Iori
and Inaba Himeko isn't going to end
because of a man.
That's what I believe.
So you don't need to worry.
You can come back to the clubroom.
Okay, I got it.
Don't blame me if you regret it later.
I'm no pushover.
If that's how you want
it, I'll be going all out.
You're going to be crushed.
Just so you know,
I don't plan on losing or giving him up.
And do you really think
you can beat me?
There are plenty of ways
to beat a girl
who's got nothing but a cute face.
Ouch...
Anyway, you were pretty intense.
Was that really me?
Wait, when did my episode—
Iori?
So, I want to set the
record straight.
What the hell?
Why did you show up now?!
Well, I wanted to tell
you that this unleashing
of desire business is about to end.
End? Is it all over?
But there's been an accident,
and I thought it would be more amusing,
or better, to let you know—
I don't understand what
you're talking about!
Yaegashi-san fell.
Huh?
Fell?
You mean he fell off that cliff?
Taichi!
This isn't like what
happened with Nagase-san.
I didn't do a thing.
So why did he fall?
That selfless freak
is really something.
Ow...
Geez, don't make us worry like that!
We ran over here for nothing!
Yeah!
Yui and I were enjoying quality
time cleaning up together.
That's irrelevant.
Oh, Inaba.
You look really pale.
Wasn't Nagase-san with you?
Listen to this.
Taichi did something stupid again.
He was trying to help a kitten
that was stuck in a tree.
And he ended up falling down.
What about the cat?
It's fine.
It's a good thing that
neither of you were hurt.
Sorry about all the trouble.
Honestly, you and your false alarms.
Well, at least we get to laugh it off.
Inaba?
What's wrong, Inaba?
Don't make me worry, idiot!
Hey, that was uncalled for.
Er, I'm sorry!
Don't cry!
I don't know what's wrong,
but it was all my fault!
I'll apologize!
So stop crying!
Inaba, you don't need to cry.
Look, Taichi's fine.
What? Were you really that worried?
You can stop crying.
Stop crying, Inaba-chan.
I finally made it back.
Iori, where did you go?
Yeah, I'm not really sure.
Um, what's wrong with Inaban?
Actually, we're not sure either.
Inaba, I'm not sure what's
wrong, but I'm sorry!
It was all my fault!
Inaba, Inaba.
You can stop crying.
Taichi's fine, Inaba-chan.
Inaban, Inaban? What's wrong?
So these episodes of our desires
getting unleashed are over.
Starting tomorrow, it's back
to working on the paper.
Is it really over?
Yeah, it might be something
else next time.
No point in worrying about that now.
We should enjoy the
freedom we have now!
Honestly...
What does it take to
never have to worry?
Huh?
What happened to Taichi and Inaba-chan?
No idea.
Maybe Fujishima-san's yelling
at them about what happened.
You think?
Oh, in that case...
We should head home then.
H-Hey, Inaba.
You wanted to talk?
Wh-What is it?
I love you!
Ah, uh...
Er...
I-I'm...
I'm happy to hear you say that.
I truly feel honored, from
the bottom of my heart.
But right now, I'm in love with Nagase.
I already knew that.
But "right now" means that
I still have a chance
to change your mind.
U-Uh, that wasn't what I meant...
Since you and Iori
aren't going out yet,
there's plenty of room for
me to worm myself in.
And I already told Iori
about this beforehand.
So don't worry.
We're going to have a fair fight,
so you can do whatever you want.
W-Wait! You're moving too fast!
What do you mean?
It almost sounds like the two
of you are fighting over me...
You took my first one without asking.
Another one can't hurt, right?
I'll see you in the clubroom tomorrow.
I'm so embarrassed I could die!
I kissed him!
I'm heading out.
What's going on, Himeko?
You usually leave
without saying a word.
Shut up, stupid.